[ Dennis ]
No, dude.
It's not-- It's not
a question of individual style.
It's about having some taste.
You're attacking my ability
to express myself, dude.
How am I attacking
your ability to--
I just don't get it.
What's not to get?
"Come to Philly for the crack."
It has a picture
of the Liberty Bell on it.
Yeah, but--
- It's funny and original.
- It's not fun-- How is it
funny and original?
Every asshole on South Street's
wearing a T-shirt with
an ironic slogan on it.
Well, excuse me if all my
T-shirts don't have a little guy
playing polo on the lapel.
You cut the sleeves off
of all your T-shirts.
What, so you can
show off your tats?
Those are really original, dude.
- They're tribal.
- Oh, they're trib-- I'm sorry.
What tribe are you from?
What? Is it, like,
an Indian tribe or--
Okay, okay, okay.
You guys gonna let me
in this game or what?
No. You're the ref.
I don't want to ref anymore.
I'd like to play, so--
You're an excellent ref.
You're a very good ref.
Yeah, I know. I'm a great ref.
I'd like to play the game now.
Are you gonna get mad? You gonna
turn into the mad munchkin?
What's the ma--
Do you represent
the Lollipop Guild, Charlie?
Do you?
[ Woman ]
Hey, Charlie.
♪ Are you the mad munchkin ♪
- ♪ He is the mad munchkin ♪
- ♪ The little mad, mad
munchkin man ♪
That's a mad munchkin dance?
Oh, okay. This is what we do?
I need to talk to you.
♪ I'm a little munchkin man ♪
It's about our son!
[ Grunting ]
Nobody wants
to hear that.
[ Dennis ] So, wait,
she's sayin' this is your son?
[ Mac ] I don't know.
Sounds like a bunch of
bullshit to me, Charlie.
I know!
I know it.
There's, like, no way
that this is possible.
Well, did you have
sex with her?
Yeah.
Okay. Did you use
birth control?
Oh, Dee, we went
to Catholic school, so--
Okay. You're allowed...
to have premarital sex,
but you're not allowed
to use birth control?
No. All right.
You're twisting words here
and, like, gettin' cute.
When did she have this kid?
It's been, like, 10 years
since I've even seen her, so--
Ten years?
What does she want?
Well, that's--
that's the weird thing.
She doesn't
want money or anything.
She just wants me to meet him.
Are you gonna do it?
No.
Well, dude, you gotta
meet the kid. I mean,
you gotta find out for sure.
Yeah, I guess.
It's just--
[ Groans ] I mean, I wish
I could go back in time and
do the right thing, you know?
- Like be there for him?
- No. Get her an abortion.
So you're not allowed
to use birth control,
but abortions are no problem?
All right. Okay.
So now you're, like,
a word genius.
And everything I say,
you twist it around
and make me look dumb.
Charlie's right though.
He should have at least
had a say in the matter.
It's her body,
and it's her decision.
No, I'm sorry.
It's not just her decision.
The man should get a vote.
- Okay. Well, ultimately
it's her choice.
- It is not just her choice.
It's nobody's choice.
It should be left up to God.
Is he-- Is that--
Are you joking?
No, it's not a joke!
You remember Genesis,
Book Two, Verse Three?
"And he breathed into the
nostrils of Adam on the first
day. And it was good."
Right in his nostrils, huh?
Sounds really uncomfortable.
You're making an asshole
out of yourself. Dude, you need
to get a blood test, okay?
I remember Stacy Corvelli.
She was a slut.
You're right. You're right.
Uh, Mac, what's God's
stance on blood tests?
Hmm. I don't know.
I'd have to check.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
All right,
you feeling good?
No. I feel nauseous.
I think I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna run.
No, no, no. It's--
I should go.
Hi. Hey, Charlie.
Hi.
Hey.
You brought your, uh--
Uh, Dennis Reynolds. We didn't
get a chance to talk before,
but I remember you. Yeah.
You went to St. Giles?
I did. Yeah.
Ah.
With-- Yeah.
So you two are
together now, or--
No.
No. No.
No. I'm just here
for moral support.
Yeah, we're not--
That's not even a--
I brought him along.
Yeah.
So--
All right.
Come on in.
[ Door Closes ]
I'm real glad you decided
to do this, Charlie.
Yeah. Well, uh, you know,
it's the least I could do, so--
Yeah. Sorry I don't
have a lot of time.
I gotta get to work.
Uh, Tommy,
come on in here, Son!
[ Tommy ]
What do you want, Mom?
He's a bit of a handful.
Uh, Charlie and his friend
are here.
[ Tommy ]
So goddamn what?
Tommy, come in here,
please!
This is bullshit.
Whoa!
[ Stacy ]
Language, please.
- Which one of you fags
is supposed to be my dad?
- Whoa, hello.
Right off the bat
with the--
Yeah.
Tommy, be nice. Huh?
This is Charlie.
[ Scoffs ]
Are you serious?
This is the guy?
What's that--
What's that supposed
to mean, buddy?
Okay. Well, I should be
home around 8:00. Uh, what do
you guys have planned?
- Uh, I thought we'd
go to the park.
- Huh. That sounds nice.
Wanna go
to the park, Tommy?
I don't care.
[ Beeping ]
Okay. That's great.
Bye, sweetie.
Have fun, boys.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
I'm not goin' to the park.
No shit.
[ Phone Ringing ]
What is this place?
Uh, this is a place
where we're gonna go see
a special friend of mine.
Why?
'Cause he's gonna help us figure
something very important out.
It's gonna be
good to know.
Why?
Because I said so. No more
questions, okay, buddy?
Why?
Stop saying "why."
Stop it.
I don't like this game.
Why? Why?
Is this a game?
This is your game?
Why? Why?
Hey, pretty boy.
What you here for?
My friend's gettin'
a... blood test.
Your boyfriend?
No. He's not my--
He's not my boyfriend.
He got AIDS?
I don't--
I don't think so.
Do you?
No, I don't.
I'll blow you for $10.
[ Blows ]
You know what?
Let me consult some
of this free literature...
they got here
regarding that proposition.
Oh. You know what?
[ Chuckles ]
According to this,
that's not really a good idea.
So I'm gonna have to pass.
But thanks. I appreciate it.
Really nice of you.
He's playin'
mind games, dude.
I wanna leave.
Hey, it's tough.
What are we doin' here?
Don't answer that.
It's a trick question.
He tries to get in your head.
It's a little game he plays.
No, let-- let me
answer the question.
See, we're at a free clinic,
Tommy. Charlie doesn't have
health insurance.
[ Whispering ]
See this lady back here?
Take a look.
That's what you get
when you don't have
health insurance.
I wanna go to the mall!
Keep your voice down.
Keep your voice--
I wanna go to the mall!
Stop yelling--
I wanna go to the--
Stop your yelling.
We need to-- Ow!
He's biting my hand!
Come on.
[ Dennis ]
Let's go. Let's go.
[ Rings ]
Sacred Right.
It's a child, not a choice.
Mm-hmm.
All righty.
I'll make sure he gets
the message. Thank you.
Hi.
So I was having an argument with
some friends the other day.
Uh-huh.
And I was wondering
if you could help me out
with some information.
Are you interested
in joining our cause?
No.
No. Actually, just looking
for some info on the Bible,
Jesus, that kind of thing.
Well, if you join our
mailing list, the reverend--
Okay, listen to me.
I don't really wanna join
your little freak show. Just
looking for some information.
So if you could point me
in the right direction,
that'd be great.
Well, we have some
literature--
Great. Thank you. Thanks.
on the display back
by the water cooler.
Oh, mama.
Hey, there.
Hi.
Hey.
Oh, are you here
to sign up for the rally?
Yes, I am.
Great.
Yeah, real excited
about the rally.
We're gonna kick ass this time.
Well, I'm ready to kick
somebody's ass, I'll tell you
what. I hate those bastards.
Wow! That's--
Uh, hate's a very strong word.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, let me
tell you something, Megan.
I hate dead baby fetuses,
you know?
I hate them
because they're dead,
and they shouldn't be.
They should be alive,
and they should be loved.
Oh! Wow!
You just--
You seem really passionate.
Yeah.
More than you know.
Nice kid, Charlie.
What the hell do you
think is wrong with that kid?
[ Pool Cues Clattering ]
You've gotta get
that blood test, dude.
- Die! Die! Die!
- No! Hey! Whoa, Tommy! No!
No! No! No!
Give me the stick!
Come on! This place sucks!
I wanna go to the mall!
We can't go to the mall,
all right?
Shut up! I'm the boss of you!
You're not the boss of me!
I am the boss!
I wanna go to the mall!
I'll show you
who's the boss of who.
Let's go to the mall!
You wanna go to the mall?
I wanna go to the mall!
You could ask nice.
Dennis, let's go.
We're goin' to the mall.
- I'm not spending any more
time with that kid.
- Come on, dude! Fine. Great.
Dee-- Dee, will you just--
Can we go to the mall?
Will you drive me?
I guess, if Dennis
watches the bar.
That's fine.
Great. Fine. Thank you.
[ Shouts ]
You're ugly.
You're ugly!
You are the one
that's ugly!
Charlie! Jesus Christ!
Are you almost 30?
Are you almost 30 years old?
Yes!
You have to
buy me a toy!
I don't have to
buy you shit.
If you don't buy me anything,
I'm gonna
tell my mom you took me
to a black people's house.
Okay.
Wow! Oh, my God, that's racist.
What do you say to that?
I don't say anything.
You still have to buy me a toy!
[ Grunting ]
Charlie, what in the hell
are you gonna do
if this kid's yours?
Oh, I don't know.
I'll probably, uh, kill myself.
Whoa!
Isn't that your waitress
from the coffee shop?
Cool. Stewie.
Oh, my God.
Go talk to her.
What? No.
Come on.
Go talk to her.
No, dude.
You've been in love
with this girl forever.
I know that. You know what?
Come with me and pretend
you're my girlfriend.
It'll make her jealous.
No. I won't do that.
Come on.
It's gonna work.
No. No, it's not.
All right. Come stand
next to me then.
Why?
So she doesn't think
I'm creepy.
Well, you are creepy.
I realize this.
That's why I need you.
All right. Let's go.
Thank you.
Stop sweating.
Then we can grab him
if you like him, okay?
Hey.
Fancy seeing you here.
Oh. Hello, Charlie.
Buying toys, are you?
Yeah.
Cool. This is my, uh--
Friend. We're good friends.
Hi.
- Is that cute little
girl your--
- I'm her big sister.
Oh.
Hmm, that's weird.
She looks Mexican.
She is Mexican.
It's the Big Sister program.
She's not my real little sister.
That is such a coincidence.
That's exactly what
we're here doing.
What?
Yeah.
Do you see that, um,
adorable little guy
over there?
[ Clicks ]
That's Charlie's
little brother.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- No way. You're involved
in the program?
Yeah!
Well, that's--
I didn't know you were
involved in the program.
I love the program!
It's one of
his favorite programs.
Yeah. I've-- I've been
in the program since--
A long time now.
I guess you're gonna
be going to the picnic then
at Fairmount Park.
Right.
Saturday?
Saturday.
Yeah. Are you there? Are you
goin'? Are you gonna be there?
I will be there
on Saturday, yes.
Great.
Maybe we'll see you there.
Maybe.
Or you know what?
Or... maybe we could carpool.
You know what I mean?
Carpool?
Yeah. Well, come on.
Think about it.
We'll save the environment.
We'll team up. It'll be good.
This is smart.
Reduce, reuse, recycle.
You should do it.
The kids will love it.
The kids--
He loves Mexicans.
All right.
Sure. Let's do it.
Oh!
Okay. Yeah.
Great.
Great. Okay, well--
Nice to meet you too.
I'll see you.
I gotta go get
my little sister. Okay, bye.
Bye.
Thank you.
You're still
pretty sweaty.
[ All Shouting ]
Baby killer! Baby killer!
Baby killer!
You bastards
are gonna burn in hell!
Abortion is murder!
It's a child, not a choice!
Pro-choice is pro-death!
Wow! Great rhetoric.
Thank you.
Hey, you're really
hard-core, aren't you?
Oh, well, you know.
I mean, if you really
wanna see hard-core--
What's this?
That's the list of doctors
I'm gonna kill.
There's two
already crossed out.
Yeah, I know.
[ Grunting ]
So you really
had a good time, huh?
Yeah. We had a blast.
Hmm. He didn't give you
any problems?
No. Not a single problem.
Uh, listen, I was thinking
maybe I could take him out
this Saturday?
Really?
Yeah, sure.
I'd pick him up at, like, 8:00?
You know,
do the father-son thing.
Are you all right?
Is that gonna be okay? Because
I could really use-- use him.
Goddamn it!
I'm sorry.
Is everything all right?
I can't do this!
Tommy's not your son.
What?
Remember Jimmy Doyle
from high school?
That son of a bitch
is Tommy's real father.
He left me six months ago.
You know what a nightmare
it's been since he left?
I don't care.
I can't raise Tommy alone.
I don't care! You thought you'd
just pawn your son off on me?
What else? I thought I could
find him a better role model
than that piece of shit!
Stop talking!
Wait. Let me think.
[ Grunts ] God!
All right. So can I still
take him out on Saturday?
Yeah.
Great.
That's pretty thin.
That might be too thin.
[ Mac ] Hey-oh!
Hey, Mac. Where you been?
Oh, I don't know.
Saving humanity.
Are you still
on this kick, dude?
Yeah, you know, Den,
I was thinking what you were
saying the other day...
about the T-shirts with
the stupid slogans on them.
And I was wondering
what you think about this?
Huh, bitch? Yeah!
Is that stupid enough for you?
You're not seriously
wearing that, are you?
You look ridiculous.
Whatever, dude.
You know, that's the problem
with you anti-abortionists.
You cry about the sanctity
of life, and then you wear
a shirt like that.
- I'm not listening to you.
- Aren't you right-wingers all
about the death penalty too?
- Does that not involve
killing somebody?
- Right, right, right.
And you liberals are
against killing murderers.
But you're for
killing innocent babies.
That's interesting.
- Yeah. We like to kill babies.
- You guys are taking this
way too seriously.
Den, you don't understand
the week I've been having.
I met a girl at one of these
organizations who is a freak.
She is the dirtiest chick
I've met in my life.
Seriously?
Yeah. You gotta come with me
to one of these rallies.
They're having
another one on Saturday.
These chicks are everywhere.
I can jump on board
with that.
Yeah!
Are you actually gonna
throw away all your convictions
for a chance to get laid?
I don't really have
any convictions.
Where is this rally
being held?
Uh, Planned Parenthood,
Bryn Mawr Medical Center.
Well, I'm gonna go.
At least one pro-choice voice
is gonna be heard.
One? There was, like,
tons of those chicks
at the last one.
- Which side had more?
- Oh, which one do you think?
The one that cares about
protecting women's bodies...
or the one that's run
by the religious right?
Probably the side
you're goin' to.
I'm gonna fight
for the right to choose.
You're a scumbag,
Dennis.
Today's a big day
for me, Tommy.
Why?
Well, today is probably the best
chance I'm ever gonna have
of hooking up with this girl.
So, uh, look at me
for a second, pal.
Okay, do me a favor.
If you're good today,
I'm gonna buy you...
anything that you want,
anything in the world,
all right?
Oh, my God!
I will smash your
face into a-- into a jelly!
Wrong key.
[ All Chanting ]
Keep abortion legal!
Stop abortion now!
This is crazy.
Yeah, weird. People actually
care about women's bodies.
You believe that?
Yeah. I think Mac
picked the wrong side.
There's, like,
no dudes here.
Gross.
You know what?
Uh, give me a second here.
Hi.
I like your look.
Excuse me?
I like the whole hippie thing.
It really works for you.
Get lost, breeder.
Oh, okay.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah. Mmm.
I love the smell of protest
in the morning.
What?
I was quoting that movie,
you know, Apocalypse Now.
"Napalm in the morning."
Is that the new
Mel Gibson movie?
No.
Did you see
Passion of the Christ?
I saw it 12 times.
Okay.
You know,
you really shouldn't joke
about the Apocalypse.
So just fill these out.
We'll get your information
in the mail.
Thanks.
"Keep your laws"--
I like your T-shirt.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Where do I sign?
Right here.
Love T-shirts like that.
Right.
So, do you come to these
kind of things often, or--
Are you hitting on me
at an abortion rally?
Yeah, I--
[ Sighs ]
You know what? I think
all these chicks are gay.
Yeah, I don't know
that they're gay.
I think they can just
smell how disgusting you are.
That sucks for me.
[ Dialing ]
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
Hello.
Hey, Mac. It's Dennis.
Uh, look, man,
there's no talent over here.
What's the deal over there?
Oh, yeah. We're lookin'
real good over here, bro.
What do you think?
Hop the fence and come over.
All right.
I'll see you in a second.
Later, gator.
All right, Megan.
I'm finished.
You are a genius.
Hey, Sis. I'm gonna jet.
You're leaving?
Uh, this side sucks.
I'm gonna try my luck
over there.
Are you kidding me?
Later, tater.
Dennis, you are
such a jackass!
[ All Shouting ]
Excuse me.
Yeah. Can I get by here?
Thanks.
[ Shouting Continues ]
I just--
I really love that sign.
I wondered that so many times.
Hey, there's a guy
on the fence.
Hey! Hey!
They're coming after us!
No. They're not coming after us.
I'll show you what we
do to them. How's your aim?
Pretty good.
But I don't think
that's such a good idea.
I don't think--
Hey, it's okay.
These people deserve this.
[ Shouting Continues ]
Yeah. He looks
like he deserves it.
Maybe just one.
Oh! Ow!
Yeah! Come on!
Get your eggs, people!
Oh, my God!
Ow!
Shit!
They're throwing eggs!
They did this last time.
I came prepared.
Oh. Hey, Dennis!
How's the action
over there, buddy?
- What?
What the hell are you doing?
- Oh! They're coming--
Now they're coming back.
[ Screams ]
Die!
Hey!
[ Groaning ]
Hot chicks on that side, Dennis?
You're gonna burn in hell!
[ Shouting ]
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Hey, guess what.
I have a surprise for you.
What?
It's a real miracle.
What is it?
I'm pregnant!
What?
You gotta get an abortion.
Megan, wait, wait, wait!
Stop talking to me!
Well, listen, I just think
our situation is different.
How is our situation different?
Well, because I didn't
mean to get you pregnant.
It was an accident.
You are so pathetic.
You can't have this kid. I'm way
too young, and I have a little
bit of an alcohol problem--
Save it!
I'm not pregnant!
What?
I'm not pregnant.
It was a test.
I just thought for, like,
one second that you
might be the one.
I just had to know for sure.
Wait a second!
So you're not pregnant?
[ Engine Starts ]
No.
And this was a test?
Yeah.
And I failed?
Have a nice life, asshole.
No! Wait-- Wait--
Wait a second! Wait! Oh.
Son of a bitch!
Where the hell have you been?
You said 11:30, dude!
I don't wanna talk about it.
That waitress is picking me up
any minute! I was ready
to shut down the bar!
- What is that kid doin' here?
- I'm taking him to the
Big Brother-Big Sister thing.
Get him out of here, Charlie.
I'm getting picked up
any minute! Will you relax?
I told you, I don't
want kids in the bar!
Dude, what is up your ass?
You-- You are out! Whoa, dude!
This kid reeks of booze!
[ Beeping ]
No, no, no, no, no.
Are you drunk? Don't be drunk.
Yeah.
How could you
let this happen?
I was the only one bartending!
He must have been takin' sips
out of people's beers.
All right.
Brew some coffee.
You can't give him coffee!
Let go of that!
Get him out of here, Charlie!
Charlie!
Okay, here we go!
Fresh air! Have a seat!
Sit down! Fresh air!
You suck!
You suck, all right?
Breathe it in. Fresh air now.
You suck and you have
an ugly face!
You suck!
You have an ugly face, okay?
You try and push people's
buttons all the time!
And you get in their head,
and you drive them crazy!
Maybe that's why you don't
have a dad anymore!
Oh, my God!
- What are you doing?
- I'm drunk.
He's drunk?
He's not drunk.
I am drunk!
You're not drunk.
He sounds drunk.
I am drunk!
You're not drunk!
Stop saying that!
He's fine.
[ Tommy Coughing ]
- Jimmy Doyle!
- Yeah?
Charlie Kelly.
Yeah?
From high school.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't recognize you
without all your acne.
Yeah.
[ Chuckling ]
All right, listen, I need
to talk to you about your kid.
Why?
Uh, let's see. Because your kid
has serious emotional problems.
Why?
I don't know. Maybe because
you're not there as a father.
Why?
You're kidding me?
This your little game?
Why?
This is what you're doin'? This
is what you're doin' to me?
Why?
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]